wheelchairindia.com 2016-04-05

# Privacy Policy : Wheelchair india Privacy Policy : Privacy Policy of Wheelchairindia

**Registration Obligations**

“Manish Steel Works” respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides succinctly the manner your data is collected and used by us. You are advised to please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services; we collect from you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions.

By accepting the Privacy Policy during registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **We respect your privacy** ****

At wheelchairindia.com, we are extremely proud of our commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Site.

We want users to:   
1\. Feel comfortable using our Site.  
2\. Feel secure in submitting information to us.  
3\. Know that by using our Site you are consenting to the collection of certain data. **Privacy Guarantee** **** ****We promise that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties (except as provided in this Privacy Policy) without your consent. We and/or certain authorized third party service providers will use the personal information provided by you to provide you with the services, which are offered on our portal. From time to time we may reveal general statistical information about our Site and visitors, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority. **Information Collected** ****  
We only collect the details provided by you on registration together with information we learn about you from your use of our service and your visits to our Site and other sites accessible from them. We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or competitions offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback or completing profile forms. We will collect only such information as is necessary and relevant to us to provide you with the services available on the Site.
